tickbox.net 2015-04-07

# Tickbox.net surveys :: Welcome to Tickbox.net online surveys

## Privacy policy

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for Tickbox.net.

Tickbox.net is committed to our members' privacy and the following notes outline our information practices. If you feel we are not abiding by our policy or if you have any questions please contact [privacy@tickbox.net](mailto:privacy@tickbox.net).

**If you feel that Tickbox.net is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should immediately contact[privacy@tickbox.net](mailto:privacy@tickbox.net) by email to resolve your concerns.**

#### Information Collection and Use

Tickbox.net is a trading name of markettiers4dc Limited who is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Tickbox.net collects information from our users at several different points on our web site.

#### Registration

In order to use this web site, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services and promotions on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide some demographic information but encouraged so we can provide a more personalised experience on our site.

#### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

#### Tracking and Cookies

Cookie Tracking: We may store information about you using cookies (files which are stored by us on your computer's internet browser or other access devices), which we can access when you visit our site in the future. We do this to facilitate a number of different functions of the Tickbox Rewards programme, for example to remember your login details and to award Tickbox Rewards into your account. We retain the information contained in cookies for the duration strictly necessary for their purpose. If you want to delete any cookies that are already on your computer at any time, you can do so through your browser. Information on deleting or controlling cookies is available at [www.AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/). Please note that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you will not be able to access the full functionality of the Tickbox Rewards programme and will be unable to earn and redeem points.

We and / or our partners, use cookies in the following ways to administer the programme:

#### Cookies to facilitate communication between us and you:

These cookies allow us to recognize you when you log into the site, keep your session active when you revisit us, show you the number of points in your account and keep your browsing session between the web server and web browser.

#### Cookies to facilitate the administration of your account:

These cookies enable us to provide you with the Tickbox Rewards programme as well as the Tickbox Panels services.

Regarding the Tickbox Panels service, we may use a cookie to track statistics on your internet usage in order to send you market research surveys that are specifically related to your usage and behaviour.

#### Cookies to monitor the performance of the website:

We install a cookie on the computer of people visiting the site who are not members of the programme, or do not identify themselves as members in order to produce statistics about the use of site preferences, the number and frequency of visits, number of pages viewed and more generally their activity on the site. This cookie allows us to improve our site to meet your needs. This cookie disappears once the visitor is identified as a member.

If you do not wish cookies to be placed on your computer for these purposes, you can delete them by clicking on the button below:

#### Remove cookies:

Tickbox.net also uses technology provided by Google using the Google Analytics cookie to compile usage statistics about the site so that we can improve it and adapt it to suit your needs. You can prevent the use of the Google Analytics cookie by downloading and installing a browser plugin available at the following address <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

For more information on the processing of your data by Google, you can see the Google Privacy Policy at the following address: <http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html>. In general, you can decide to accept or delete cookies by configuring your web browser. Please note that if you decide to uninstall cookies via your browser, your browsing experience on the site will be affected and we will not be able to provide you with the programme, including the awarding any points you may have earned.

Tickbox.net members may click through and open mail tracking when sent emails. This allows Tickbox.net the ability to credit any points associated to the mail and profile the recipients of our communications. We may also use this information to create a more detailed profile of you so that we can provide you with similar products that maybe of interest to you.

When you visit our site, we may also log your IP address, a unique identifier for your computer or other access device.

#### Sharing

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and clients. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

We use outside shipping companies to ship orders or prizes. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

On occasions we partner with other parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

#### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Tickbox.net is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.

#### Newsletter

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.

#### Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as postcode, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of market research or monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

### Tickbox Rewards

#### Personal Information

We collect basic personal information (Name, Address, Region, DOB, Gender, Marital Status, email address etc.) from you as part of our registration process to enable us set up your Tickbox Rewards account.

In addition we collect information on your preferences when you complete our on-line questionnaire and our polls.

We also collect information on your shopping & online activities with our partners as part of allocating Tickbox Rewards to your account.

From time to time we may also ask for additional personal information as part of a promotion/competition.

#### Use of Information

By joining the Tickbox Rewards Programme you agree that we can communicate with you with suitable offers from Tickbox Rewards, which may contain opportunities to earn and redeem points as well as to inform you of programme.

You may at any time remove yourself from the Tickbox Rewards programme in which case no additional communication will be sent from Tickbox.net to that particular account and after 30 days any Tickbox Rewards points in that account will be forfeited. Please email: [support@tickbox.net](mailto:support@tickbox.net).

From time to time we will perform analysis on our member and transaction databases. The results of this analysis may be released to third parties, but only in aggregate form and will contain no personal information at all. We may also use transactional data to update your profile so that we can offer you similar products that maybe of interest to you based on this data.

In accordance with the Data Protection Act, you have a right to access, rectify and delete nominative information concerning you. You can also object to the collection of your personal information for legitimate reasons. If at any time you wish to exercise your rights please send a request by registered letter with acknowledgment of receipt along with your username, your email address, your mailing address and your copy of ID to the Tickbox.net address listed on our [Contact Us](http://www.tickbox.net/contact.php?SES=6db49ebd78fa92dad8978ce24000797c&frmnd=dataprotection) page. Please note that in this circumstance we will be unable to administer your account effectively and it will therefore be closed.

Any confidentiality request that does not contain the username, email address, postal address and a copy of identification of the Member will be systematically rejected.

Tickbox.net cannot be held responsible for any activity in your Tickbox Rewards account that has resulted from a member not keeping their account details secure.

#### Tell-A-Friend

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. Tickbox.net will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Tickbox.net stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. The friend may contact Tickbox.net at [www.tickbox.net](http://www.tickbox.net/) to request the removal of this information from their database. 

#### Security

This web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, your information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration form asks users to enter sensitive information we do everything in our power to protect user-information online and off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, an account handler or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected log-in screens to gain entry to restricted information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment.

#### Passwords

Access to your account is password protected and we never release details of this to third parties. These details will only be released to the account holder. If you have forgotten your password, please visit the Tickbox.net Home page and follow the "[Forgotten your password](http://www.tickbox.net/recovery.php?SES=6db49ebd78fa92dad8978ce24000797c&frmnd=dataprotection)" link.

#### Supplementation of Information

In order for this web site to enhance its ability to tailor the site to an individual's preference, we combine information about the preferences and habits of users with similar information from our partners to create personalised user profiles.

#### Special Offers

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify registration. Established members will occasionally receive information on special deals and promotions. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.

#### Site and Service Updates

We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their preferences.

#### Correction/Updating Personal Information

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as your postcode), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavour to provide a way to correct or update that user’s personal data provided to us. This can usually be done once logged in members can change their details through the "View/Edit my profile" option or by emailing our Customer Support ([support@tickbox.net](mailto:support@tickbox.net)). If a member wishes to be removed from our mailing list they can do so by emailing our Customer Support ([support@tickbox.net](mailto:support@tickbox.net)).

#### Choice/Opt-in

Our users are given the opportunity to ‘opt-in’ to have their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, one of our surveys may have an ‘opt-in’ mechanism so users can receive relevant information or marketing materials from our partners.

Users who no longer wish to receive our promotional materials, or newsletter may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at [support@tickbox.net](mailto:support@tickbox.net)

Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.

#### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post a note of changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

#### General

We reserve the right to access and disclose individual information to comply with applicable laws and lawful government requests. We also reserve the rights to disclose individually identifiable information to third parties where a complaint arises concerning your use of this web site, where that use does not comply with our terms and conditions
